[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[NURSE] It's done.
Your father has abandoned us.
He has a new family in Manila.
He cheated on me. He cheated on us!
He chose his mistress
and their illegitimate child!
They are to blame for your sister's death!
Damn them. Damn all of them.
Damn them!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Um, Auntie Pres, this will be your room.
And this'll be mine.
And Oliver will stay there.
As well as Dad.
You're letting your father
live here with us?
[BILLY] What he did to my brother
and me isn't easy to forget.
But I also can't forget
what he did for us.
Look at this.
I had this printed myself!
Looks good, huh?
Before, we used to just be
together in photos.
Now, we really are together!
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Pa?
- [MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENRICO CRYING]
Pa?
- [MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENRICO KEEPS CRYING]
Thank you.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
I found these.
I've read all of them too.
Those were for every year
that I couldn't be with you, Billy.
Would it be okay if I asked for a hug?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
Ma.
No matter what happens,
don't tell them
that you know
they're Papa's second family.
Why not?
That's the truth.
Ma.
Please listen to me.
That's a strong motive.
It'll just prove that you're going after
Papa's illegitimate child.
We'll get into more trouble.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But
shouldn't they be the ones to suffer?
Right?
Not us.
Especially not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
[SNIFFLES]
I never meant for this to happen.
But when I saw their house burning down,
I thought that they deserved it.
So they could go through
what happened to us.
What happened to your sister.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But it's also my fault, Ma.
I was followed. [CLICKS TONGUE]
They tracked us down,
and now look where we are.
Behind bars.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I will do everything possible, Ma.
I will do everything I can
to get you out of here.
Not just me.
Both of us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
DAILY NEWS
FIRE BURNS DOWN HOME
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir Enrico.
I'm Private Investigator Jimenez.
Uh…
Have you found my wife and daughters?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Your eldest daughter, Abigail?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
She died in a fire.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
FIRE BURNS DOWN HOME
How are Mariela and Bea doing?
What happened to them?
As for Mariela,
she was taken to a mental institution
and got confined there for years.
Bea had her discharged.
After that, there's been no news
or information about them I could find.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where is my eldest daughter buried?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENRICO EXHALES SHARPLY]
Abi, dear…
I'm sorry.
I wasn't a good father to you and Bea.
I promise…
I will find your mother and sister.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE]
[ENRICO] Please forgive me, Olive.
I wasn't with you when you
gave birth to Oliver.
You know, I've always wondered,
"What if you'd been there
the night Oliver was born?"
"Would Mama still be alive?"
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I was so afraid back then.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [RAIN POURING]
It was just me and Mama,
and no one helped us.
I kept praying for you to come.
I badly wished you were there.
Because I knew that if you were there,
you wouldn't abandon us.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
But my prayer didn't work.
You didn't come.
I was helpless.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry.
[ENRICO SOBBING]
I hope you can all forgive me.
[ENRICO BREATHES DEEPLY]
[ENRICO SNIFFLES, SOBS]
[ENRICO SOBS, SNIFFLES]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENRICO SOBBING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't know if Billy will ever
be able to forgive me
for what I'm about to tell her.
I know this is too much.
But she needs to know the truth.
[DETERMINED MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[DETERMINED MUSIC CONTINUES]
Attorney, my mother can't stay here long.
She tried to take
her own life in the past.
What if she does it here too?
Are you saying your mother has
a history of mental distress?
Yes. Why?
That's no guarantee she won't go to jail.
The evidence against her is strong.
But we can argue
she wasn't in her right mind.
It could be a mitigating factor
for her penalty.
Her sentence might even be reduced.
And in some cases,
the judge orders treatment
instead of prison time.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What about me?
What can I do
to get out of here, Attorney?
[MUSIC BECOMES UNEASY]
Multiple charges were
filed against you by Benilda Cariño.
One way to approach this is
through amicable settlement.
[INHALES SHARPLY] What is
an amicable settlement?
Please explain it to me.
Aside from paying the damages
and signing an agreement,
you need to apologize to the victim.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Apologize?
Me, apologize?
I should apologize?!
I will never apologize to that woman!
That viper! Me, really?!
She's the one who should apologize to me!
She should apologize to me and my mother!
Bea, calm down.
For me to help you properly,
you need to tell me why
you're so angry at Ms. Cariño.
Everything you tell me is confidential.
What really happened?
[OMINOUS MUSIC SWELLS, THEN FADES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, are you sure you're ready?
We don't really have a choice.
LoveList can't afford to slow down now.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Team…
I know I've been away for a few days,
so thank you for holding the fort
while I was gone.
Anyway, we have a lot to cover today.
Possible investors, um…
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Expansion of LoveList, um…
Um… cybersecurity updates,
and competitors report.
Right.
So to start,
Claire Fabrizio
has officially expressed her interest
in investing
in LoveList's global expansion.
Claire Fabrizio?
Peter's wife?
Ex-wife soon, apparently.
Anyway, she's the first one
to show interest in us,
so if she likes our projections
and presentation,
we still have a chance to close the deal.
And she also filed for divorce from Peter.
So all our firm correspondence
will go straight to Claire.
Mm-hmm. She's divorcing him?
Good for her, as she should.
Mm-hmm. And hopefully,
their investment goes through.
Well, we just need
to revise the presentation,
reflecting all the adjustments made
to the cybersecurity rollout.
Let's coordinate Jordan on that.
Okay.
Toni, I need solid numbers
on projected ROI,
revenue growth forecast,
and how fast we can recover
operational costs
once we start with the expansion.
Yes, chief.
Jumping in on the budget discussion,
I'll also present the projected cost
for our new security upgrades.
Metal scanners,
dedicated LoveLine holding areas,
additional security personnel…
How bad are the numbers?
Honestly,
they are pretty high, chief.
Then we really don't have a choice.
We need to close this deal
with Claire Fabrizio.
Okay?
Okay.
[TONI] Yes.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I LOVE YOU, BABE. GO EAT.
WE JUST FINISHED DINNER, BABE.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
- [ROWENA] We rarely hang out.
- [RALPH] It's great here, babe.
- [CHARM] Really?
- [RALPH] Yup.
They have the best steak and…
[LOUNGE MUSIC PLAYING]
Should we go somewhere else? Yeah?
Ralph! Son.
[ROWENA] Ralph, hi!
Come, come.
My son.
Say hi to your aunties.
- Ah…
- [ROWENA] My son, Ralph.
Hello.
I heard the news.
They caught the person ruining LoveList,
and the mom who set fire to Billy's house?
The drama of that company, it never ends.
Ma, please. Come on.
I told you, it's a mess there.
That company is bound to fail
sooner or later.
Get out while you still can.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SETS GLASS DOWN]
- Okay.
You know I just want
what's best for you, son.
What's best for me?
What's best for me
is for you to stop controlling
all my decisions.
Wow.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm doing all this for your sake.
For your future.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISPERS] Babe, let's go?
Excuse us.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma.
I spoke with the lawyer.
She said it's possible
you'll be moved to a hospital.
Isn't that great, Ma?
You won't rot here anymore.
You can get out.
Which hospital?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
The…
ward.
- Crazy. She's going to a psych ward.
- [MARIELA] Wait, the psych ward?
- What am I, crazy?
- [LAUGHS] She admitted it.
You want to be away from me, right?
- [WOMAN] It came from her.
- Ma, no. You're not crazy.
Ma, just think about it.
You'll be better off there.
You'll be taken care of.
Turns out she really is crazy.
- [WOMEN CACKLING]
- She belongs there.
- Hey!
- Ma. Hey, Ma!
- Let go of me! Ouch!
- Stop it, Ma!
- [WOMAN] Stay out of this!
- [BEA] What the hell?!
- Stop it!
- Ma! Ma!
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Ma!
- Miss! Miss, help! Help!
- [WOMAN] Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Hey! What's going on there?!
- Hey! Here she comes!
[WOMAN] They started it! They're psychos!
Stop it! Quiet down!
My mother needs a doctor!
Miss, call a doctor!
My mother needs one now!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[YANI] Toni said it was just going to be
you two celebrating.
What happened?
[RALPH] We wanted to celebrate
with you guys.
It's more fun to celebrate
with friends, right?
- Billy.
- This is about Charm and Ralph.
Let's stop stressing out.
You want me to get sent
to the mental hospital.
I don't want to! I don't want to!
[DINO] What do you want?
I know about your plan.
[DINO] Keep your mouth shut.
Let me join your group.
I know someone.
He can give us new names
and a new life.
[CHARM] Just fix your relationship
with your mom first.
Just look at Billy.
She chose to forgive.
[RALPH] Can you, like,
honestly say that,
you know, things are
getting better?
♪ My heart won't be lost ♪
♪ Even if you let go, I'll come back ♪
[JORDAN] I thought
you went home?
I just wanted to ask something.
What is it?
Are we okay?
What do you mean?
There's something you're not telling me.